为什么你快死了 妈妈？
Why are you dying, Mama?
我的时候到了
It's my time.
因为我的时候到了
It's just my time.
现在…
Oh, now...
你不用害怕 宝贝
don't you be afraid, sweet heart .
死亡只是生命的一部分
Death is just a part of life .
是我们注定要面对的
Something we're all destined to do.
我并不知道
I didn't know it,
但我注定要做你的妈妈
but I was destined to be your mama.
我就尽力做好
I did the best I could.
你做得很好
You did good.
嗯…我相信你能实现自己的命运
Well...I happen to believe you make your own destiny .
你要凭着上帝所给予的做到最好
You have to do the best with what God gave you.
我的命运是什么 妈妈？
What's my destiny, Mama?
你要自己去弄明白
You're going to have to figure that out for yourself.
人生就像一盒各式各样的巧克力
Life is a box of chocolates, Forrest.
你永远不知道下一块将会是哪种
You never know what you're going to get.
妈妈总有办法把事情说清楚
Mama always hada way of explaining things
让我也能听明白
so I could understand them.
我会想念你的 福雷斯
I will miss you, Forrest.
她得了癌症
She had got the cancer
在星期二去世了
and died on a Tuesday.
我给她买了顶新帽子
I bought her a new hat
上面有很多小花
with little flowers on it.
我要说的说是这么多了
And that's all I have to say about that.